時は戦国、乱世の時代。
からくり人の住むジパング国では群雄割拠して合戦に明け暮れ、
からくり武芸者たちも勝利と栄光を目指してしのぎを削っていた。
そしていま、からくり武芸者ナンバー１を目指す、とてつもないヒーローが誕生した！
ムサシ、見参でござるだス！
からくり剣豪伝ムサシロード
男はいつでも　世界の真ん中で
いちばん　強くなる日を
AH! AH! 夢見て
心の刃　大空にふりかざし
冒険の旅の　幕を開ける
ジパング国を　さすらう剣豪
その名　からくりびと　ムサシ
GO! FIGHT!
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　昨日よりも　今日　強い
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
明日は　輝くぞ
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　思い切りと　静けさと
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
みけんが　きらめいた　ムサシ！！
난처한 상황에 처한 마을 사람들을 돕기 위해 센히메 일행은 슈텐타이거가 조종하는 야마타노오로치하고 싸워 쓰러뜨렸다.
To help troubled villagers, Senhime's group fought against and took down Yamata no Orochi under Shutentiger's cotrol.
그리고 무사시는 야마타노오로치가 숨기고 있던 천구환을 손에 넣는 데 성공했다.
And Musashi managed to obtain Tenkūmaru, hidden inside Yamata no Orochi.
이것으로 이도류 완성에 한 보 더 다가간 것이다.
By this, he is one step closer to the mastery of the technique of dual blades.
금으로 번쩍이는 도둑, 고에몬도이오
The Ultimate Thief of
Shining Gold, Goemondo
네이놈, 무사시, 코지로 놈.
Damned Musashi and Kojirō...
어이, 고에몬도하고 아직 연락은 닿지 않는가.
Is Goemondo not in touch yet?
그, 그게... 모든 방법을 썼지만 아직 연락이 닿지 않습니다.
T- that's... we did everything we could, but he still is out of reach.
그 녀석...
That lazy...
몇번이고 성실하게 임무에 임하라고 말했을 텐데...
Countless times have I told him to give it his all on the job...
어떻게든 고에몬도하고 연락이 닿게 만들어라!
Contact Goemondo no matter the cost!
예!
Yessir!
그 쯤, 무사시 일행은 야마가타 가까이 있는 산중에 있었다.
Meanwhile, Musashi's group was in mountain around Yamagata.
누구시오?
Who is it-dasu?
나야!
It's me!
오센짱! 방해하면 곤란하오!
Osenchan! Don't interrupt me like that-dasu!
그래도 지루한걸.
But I'm bored.
저기! 나, 놀고 있는 게 아니오!
Hey! I am not playing-dasu!
이도류를 고안하기 위해 필사적으로 연구하고 있던 참이오!
I was training to develop the technique of dual blades-dasu!
그렇게 놀 상대를 원하면 코지로하고 놀면 되오!
If you want someone to play with that much, then go play with Kojirō-dasu!
싫어! 코지로는 너무 진지해서 재미없어.
No way! Kojirō's always too serious and he's no fun.
음, 역시 이 정도로 휘두르는 게 제일이다.
Alright. This rotation is just right.
있잖아, 놀 거 아니라면 빨리 산 밖으로 나가자.
Hey, if you're not going to play, then let's get out of the mountain as soon as possible.
그래도 나 이도류를...
But I have to train my technique of dual blades...
내 말이 안 들려? 그럼 할아버지한테 부탁해서 참수시켜버린다!
Can't you hear me? Then I'll ask my grandpa to decapitate you!
그, 그건... 알겠소.
T- that's... All right-dasu.
어이, 거기 당신들.
Hey, you people over there.
그런 곳에서 뭘 하고 있는가.
What are you doing here?
검의 수행이오.
To train my sword skills-dasu.
검의 수행? 수상한 놈이군. 잡아라!
Train your sword skills? That sounds suspicious. Get them!
어라, 잘 생긴 남자잖아.
What a handsome man!
오센짱, 위험하오!
Osenchan, get back-dasu!
갑자기 달려들다니 비겁하오! 이렇게 된 바 달려드는 불꽃은 전부 제거할 뿐이오.
It's cowardly to rush at me all of sudden-dasu! That leaves me no choice but to get rid of all those sparks jumping to me-dasu.
수상한 물건을 가지고 있다니 역시 고에몬도의 동료겠군.
Yielding such a suspicious thing also must be telling that you're working for Goemondo.
고에몬도라니 누구이오?
Who is Goemondo-dasu?
쉽소!
Easy thing-dasu!
코지로!
Kojirō!
또 동료가 있다는 것인가...
More comrades?
덕분에 살았소!
You saved me-dasu!
무사시, 넌 충분히 필사적이지 못하다! 그따위로 해서 이도류를 개안하는 일 따위가 될 것 같냐!
Musashi, you are not desperate enough! You are never opening your eyes to dual blades at that rate!
뭣이오?!
What did you say-dasu?!
빈틈이다!
Chink in the armor!
기다려 주십시오. 무슨 일이 있는지는 모르지만 저희는 절대 수상한 자가 아닙니다.
Please wait. While I am not sure about what was going on, but we swear that we do nothing suspicious.
그런 거짓말에 넘어갈 생각은 없다!
I do not intend to be fooled over such lie!
끝장내 주겠다!
Let me settle this!
그만하라!
Stop! Freeze!
여기 있는 내가 누군지 아느냐. 지팡구 넘버 원의 관동을 지배하는 제너럴 이에야스의 손녀, 센히메이다!
I am Senhime, the granddaughter of General Ieyasu, the ruler of Kantō, the number one of Jipangu!
에이! 건방지다! 허리를 숙여라!
You are being impudent! Lower your heads!
예!
Yessir!
변명하지 않겠습니다. 말도 안 되는 실례를!
I am not going to make excuses on our grave discourtesy.
알았어, 알았어! 이제 됐으니까 몸 펴.
Alright, alright! You can straighten yourself.
그래도 어째서 저희를 덮쳤습니까.
But still, why did you attack us?
그게, 고에몬도 일당으로 착각했습니다.
We confused with Goemondo's clan.
그 고에몬도라는 자는 어떤 자이오?
Who is Goemondo-dasu?
이 야마가타 성을 약탈하고 혼란에 빠뜨리려 하는 대도둑입니다. 고에몬도는 신출귀몰은 물론이고 검술 실력도 터무니없이 좋습니다.
He is a grand thief who tries to plunder this Yamagata castle and bring chaos.
He is elusive and his swordsmanship is excellent to the extent of not making any sense.
게다가 거대한 지네를 조종해서 잡는 것이 불가능합니다.
Moreover, it is impossible to catch him because of the giant centipede he controls.
쉽게 기분이 오락가락하는 고에몬도는 뻔뻔하기까지!
Not only Goemondo flatters himself all the time, but also he's shameless!
(鯱: 샤치호코, 성곽 등의 용마루 양단에 장식해 놓는, 머리는 호랑이 같고 등에는 가시가 돋친 곤두선 물고기 모양의 장식물)
(鯱: Shachihoko, an ornament with a form of mythical carp with the head of a lion and the body of a fish)
이번엔 우리 야마가타 성 지붕의 금장식을 훔치겠다고 예고장을 보내 왔습니다.
This time, he sent an advance notice that he'll steal the gold ornament at the top of our Yamagata castle.
예고한 시기는 오늘 밤. 그러나 이러지도 저러지도 못하고 있습니다.
Today is the day of that notice, but it's not like we can handle that.
직접 진두에 서서 고에몬도를 잡으려고 하고 있으나...
I was trying to catch Goemondo as the leader, but...
그래서 우릴 고에몬도의 동료로 잘못 생각했던 것이오.
So that's why you confused us as Goemondo's comrades-dasu.
대단히 죄송합니다.
It's inexcusable.
그 장식은 우리 야마가타 가의 심볼입니다. 그것을 도둑맞아서는 저희 일족은 더 이상 살아있을 수 없게 됩니다.
That ornament is the symbol of our Yamagata family. We wouldn't worth to live anymore if it gets stolen.
미남자를 울게 둘 수는 없어.
I can't let a pretty man cry.
-무사시! 코지로! 고에몬도를 잡는 걸 도와!
-예.
-Musashi! Kojirō! Help them get Goemondo!
-Alright.
이렇게나 많은 사람이 지키고 있으면 아무리 대도둑이라고 해도 훔치는 건 무리겠소.
So many people are standing guard! Not even a grand thief will manage to steal these-dasu.
그래도 처음부터 끝까지 주의해야 한다는 말도 있다.
But that does not mean that you can let your guards down.
코지로!
Kojirō!
어?
Huh?
화장실일까나...
Probably toilet-dasu...
드디어 둘이서만 있게 되었네요, 슌노스케 님.
Finally we're alone together, Shunnosuke.
그, 그래도, 저는 경비를 해야...
B- but I must keep doing my guard duties...
그런 건 무사시하고 코지로한테 맡기면 돼요.
You can leave them to Musashi and Kojirō.
그래도, 센히메 님...
But, Senhime...
그런 딱딱한 말 하지 말고, 오센짱이라 불러 봐요.
Don't be so formal; call me Osenchan!
오- 오센짱입니까.
S- Osenchan?
더 상냥하게 불러줘.
More gently.
오센짱!
Osenchan!
오, 좋아.
Perfect.
모처럼의 분위기를 부수냐!
You are destroying the mood of a while!
잠깐, 코지로!
Hey, Kojirō!
너 거기서 뭘 하고 놀고 있는 거야?
What are you playing with over there?
아니, 저는 놀고 있는 것이 아닙니다. 저것을 만들고 있습니다.
No, I am not playing. We were making those.
그렇군요. 가짜를 만들고 있었군요.
I see. You were making substitutes.
역시 슌노스케 님. 통찰이 빠르시군요.
Mr. Shunnosuke, you have a good insight.
미남자, 머리도 잘 돌아가네!
You're one pretty man with a good brain!
오쯔루 뭐하고 있을지 궁금하오...
I wonder what is Otsuru doing-dasu...
이미 잘 자고 있을 것이오.
She should be sleeping well by now-dasu.
오쯔루가 만들어주는 주먹밥이 먹고 싶소!
I want to have Otsuru's rice balls-dasu!
갑자기 추워졌소. 그리고 화장실 가고 싶어졌소. 참을 수 없소!
It got cold suddenly... and I need to go to toilet-dasu. I can't hold-dasu!
자, 서둘러서 진품하고 교체하자.
Let's hurry up and replace with the real one.
여긴 변소. 그러니까, 화장실이다.
This is a privy. In other word, a toilet.
속이 시원하오.
I'm relieved-dasu.
어라? 이런 곳에 어째서 지붕의 금장식이 있는 것이오?
Huh? Why are there the ornaments from the roof-dasu?
그렇소! 뭘 할지 생각났소!
That's it! I know what to do-dasu!
예고한 시간이다.
It's time.
코지로, 바꿔치는 건 잘 됐어?
Kojirō, did the replacing go well?
예. 확실하게 해 두었습니다.
Yes. It's perfectly done.
영주님, 고에몬도 놈, 이만큼의 경비를 보고 포기한 것일지도요!
Lord, Goemondo might gave up stealing from all these guards we posted!
음, 그러면 좋겠다만.
I do hope so.
어이! 달아나지 마라! 싸워라!
Hey! Do not run away! Fight!
안 돼, 이건 미끼다.
No, this is a bait!
무사시! 방심하지 마라!
Musashi! Do not let your guards down!
고에몬도 놈, 어디서 올 셈이오!
Goemondo, where are you coming from-dasu?!
해치워 주겠소!
I'll take you down at once-dasu!
고에몬도
Goemondo
절경이군, 절경이야! 지팡구 넘버원의 대도둑, 고에몬도!
What a sightly sight! I am Goemondo, the number one grand thief of Jipangu!
예고한 대로 그 금장식 가져가러 납셨다!
As I gave notice, I am here to take that gold ornament!
하늘에서 오다니 비겁하오!
Coming from the sky is cowardly-dasu!
도둑에게 비겁하다니 가소롭기 짝이 없군! 금장식은 가져가겠다!
How absurd, to call a thief cowardly! I'll take the ornament nonetheless!
절대 그러지 못할 것이오!
That will not happen no matter what-dasu!
연막을 쓰다니 이 얼마나 비겁한 놈이오!
Using smokescreen is the sign of ultimate cowardliness-dasu!
약속대로 금장식은 가져가신다!
As I promised, I'm taking the gold ornament!
멈추시오!
Stop right there-dasu!
잘 됐소.
This worked well-dasu.
그대로 괜찮겠느냐, 무사시! 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Are you sure about that, Musashi?! Wait for the stormy latter half!
뭐야? 금장식을 바꿔챘다고?!
What?! You replaced the ornaments?!
그렇소! 화장실 옆 방에 있는 것하고 진품하고 바꾸어 두었소!
That's right-dasu! I replaced the ones next to the toilet with the real one-dasu!
바보야! 그게 진짜였다!
You idiot! Those were the real ones!
저 방에 있는 장식이야말로 내가 바꿔친 진품이었다!
The ornaments in that room were the real ones that I've replaced!
어, 코지로가 진짜하고 가짜를 바꾸고...
Um, Kojirō replaced the real ones and fake ones...
내가 가짜를 진짜로 바꾸고...
and I replaced the fake ones to the real ones...
그러니까, 훔쳐진 건 내가 바꾼 거니까...
That means the stolen one is the one I've replaced...
진짜는 가짜하고...
The real ones and fake ones are...
에이, 답답한 놈! 봐라, 무사시!
You blockhead! Just look, Musashi!
이제 끝이다.
It's all over.
이제는...
Leaves no choice...
영주님! 자결해서는 안 됩니다!
Lord! Don't even think about it!
금장식은 이 슌노스케가 목숨을 걸고라서도 되찾아 보이겠습니다!
I, Shunnosuke, will take the ornaments back no matter what!
금장식을 되찾으러 갈 거라면 우리도 가겠어.
If you're willing to get those back, then we're going too.
그, 그런! 센히메 님을 위험에 처하게 할 순 없습니다!
N- no way! I cannot let something bad happen to Senhime!
아니, 괜찮아. 훔쳐진 건 우리 책임도 있어.
No, it's alright. It's partially our responsibility too.
그치, 무사시?!
Right, Musashi?!
그, 그렇소.
Y- yessir-dasu.
그래도...
But...
부탁이야. 데려가 줘. 네 옆을 지키게 해 줘.
Please. Take me with you. Let me be with you.
내 작은 가슴이 찌부러져버릴 거야.
My small chest is gonna be crushed.
으악, 살려주시오!
Help me-dasu!
무섭소!
I'm scared-dasu!
나, 고소공포증이오!
I have a fear of heights-dasu!
야! 벌벌 떨고 있지만 말고 정신 차리고 눈 열고 고에몬도의 아지트를 찾아라!
Hey! Quit being a scaredy cat and use your eyes to look for Goemondo's hideout!
훔쳐진 건 죄다 니 책임이니까!
It's all your fault that it got stolen!
그런 말을 해도 무서운 건 무섭소!
Whatever you say, what's scary is scary-dasu!
안 보이오!
I can't see-dasu!
아, 찾았소!
Hey, I found it-dasu!
잘 들으세요. 어떤 장치가 있을 지 모르니 충분히 조심해 주세요.
Keep in mind that we don't know what kind of contraption is installed here, so please be careful.
오, 이 줄은 뭣이오?
Oh, what is this rope for-dasu?
조심하라고 말했는데!
I just said to be careful!
도둑집에 몰래 들어오다니 거 아주 천번은 괘씸한 놈들이구나!
Sneaking into a house of thief was outrageous!
어떻게 해 주실까나.
Now, what should I do to you?
야! 고에몬도! 훔친 금장식을 돌려주시오!
Hey! Goemondo! Give the stolen ornament back-dasu!
멍청한 놈! 해변의 잔모래가 없어지더라도 세상에 도둑의 씨앗은 없어지지 않으리!
You idiot! There is an end to sands by a seashore, but there is no end to seeds of thieves!
이 세상에 있는 모든 것은 고에몬도 님의 것이다!
Everything in this world belongs to Goemondo!
금장식 따위를 훔쳐서 어쩔 셈이냐!
What are you planning to do with that stolen ornament?!
알고 싶다면 말씀해 드려야지!
If you want to know, then let me tell you!
-알고 싶지 않소!
-어라
-I don't want to know-dasu!
-Err
그래도 불쌍하니까 들어는 주겠소.
But I'll listen just because you're pitiful-dasu.
매우 고맙소이다.
Thank you very much.
안 보이오!
I can't see-dasu!
절경이군, 절경이야! 이것이야말로 천하의 고에몬도 님에게 어울리는 순금 전신상이다.
What a sightly sight! This pure gold statue fits perfectly for Goemondo, the number one grand thief of Jipangu!
지금까지는 재료가 부족해서 작업이 느려졌지만 이만큼의 금이 있다면 이미 완성된 것이나 마찬가지다!
The work had to be delayed because there wasn't enough materials, but with this much gold, it's as if already completed!
뭐야? 금장식을 녹일 생각인가?!
What?! Are you planning to melt the ornament?!
그게 맞다!
That's right!
네이놈, 그러도록 냅둘까보냐!
You bastard! I won't let that ever happen!
호오, 그렇게나 소중한 장식이라면 녹인 금에 너희들을 같이 굳혀 드릴까나!
Oh, if those are so valuable, then let me include you into the molten gold from the ornament!
그런 거 싫어! 난 제너럴 이에야스의 손녀, 센히메다! 네게 명령한다!
I don't want that! I am Senhime, the granddaughter of General Ieyasu! I'm ordering you!
이 줄을 바로 풀어라!
Untie this rope right now!
흥, 제너럴 이에야스의 손녀든 효자손이든 관계 없다! 그 이 장소를 안 이상 살아서 돌아갈 수는 없을 테니 말이지!
Hmph, it doesn't matter if you're a granddaughter of General Ieyasu or grandfailure!
Since you found out about this place, you're not going back alive!
어? 오, 이건 카라쿠리 부엉이 아닌가.
Huh? Oh, aren't you Karakuri Owl?
응? 어디 보자. 곧장 센히메를 유괴해 오라?
Let's see. Kidnap Senhime right away?
오, 이건 우연이군, 우연이야! 나쁜 일을 하고 있어도 좋은 일이 되기도 하네!
What a coincidence! Good things do follow bad things!
으악, 살려주시오! 죽고 싶지 않소!
Spare my life! I don't want to die-dasu!
멋진 무예가는 단념할 땐 깔끔하게! 조용히 해라! 살 수 있을 것 같냐!
A great martial artist knows when to go! Be quiet! It's not like you can live!
그래도 결박된 채로 동상이 되는 건 내 프라이드가 용서하지 못한다!
But still, my pride cannot forgive becoming a statue when I'm bound!
어떻게든 멋진 포즈로 만들어 줘!
Make a great-looking statue out of me!
흥! 너희같은 애송이가 금상이 된다는 것만으로도 고마운 줄 알아라!
Hmph! You should be thankful with becoming gold statues when you're nothing more than little brats!
젠장, 무념이다.
Damn it. How mortifying.
좀만 기다려, 모두. 지금 구해줄 테니까.
Soon, everyone, I'm going to save all of you.
이렇게 된 바 최후의 수단이야.
This is the last resort.
살았소...
We're saved-dasu...
공주! 방해하면 안 된다!
Princess! Do not interfere!
이 무슨 장난꾸러기 공주구나! 벌을 주어야만 하겠어.
What a naughty princess! I must give you a punishment.
벌을 받는 건 네 쪽이오!
You're the one who's going to receive punishment!
잘도 우리를 동상으로 만들려고 했겠소! 용서할 수 없소!
How dare you try to make us into statues-dasu?! Unforgivable-dasu!
내가 꼴사나운 모습을 보이게 하다니 이 은혜는 어떻게든 갚아 주어야겠어!
I must pay this back too, for making a fool out of me!
흥! 날 쓰러뜨리기에는 100년하고도 3일은 모자르다!
Hmph! You're 100 years and 3 days too early to take me down!
고에고에몬도 아몬드...
Goegoemondo Almond...
이랴! 저 꼬맹이들을 밟아 부수어 줘라!
Go! Crush those tiny brats flat!
잘 했어, 코지로!
Good job, Kojirō!
훌륭하십니다!
You are excellent!
쳇, 마침 내가 이도류로 끝내주겠다고 생각하고 있었더니...
Hmph, right when I was about to take care of him with my dual blades...
어?
Huh?
어라, 어떻게 된 일이오?
What is going on-dasu?
겨우 그런 걸로 쓰러질 거대 지네가 아니다!
That is no way taking my giant centipede down!
자, 해치워라!
Get rid of them!
그 독바늘에 찔리면 앗 소리내다 죽는다?
If you get stung with that poisoned needle, ah! and you'll be dead!
이대로는 당하고 마오!
At this rate, I'll be done for-dasu!
에잇, 난 이도류이오!
I use dual blades-dasu!
나, 이도류를 개안했소.
I finally opened my eyes towards dual blades.
뭐야?! 네이놈, 꼬맹아!
What?! Curse you!
빈틈이다!
Chink in the armor!
역시 코지로!
That's Kojirō I know!
무사시야말로 드디어 이도류를 개안했구나.
Musashi, you are the one to be praised, for opening your eyes towards dual blades.
수줍소!
I'm embarrassed-dasu!
-잘 됐네요, 슌노스케 씨.
-예.
-Everything worked out well, Shunnosuke.
-Right.
감사합니다, 센히메 님. 공주님 덕분에 훌륭한 장식이 완성되었습니다.
Thank you, Senhime. We now have a great ornament thanks to you, princess.
별 거 아니야! 보답을 바란다고는 절대 말하지는 않을 테니까.
It's nothing! I wouldn't say that I helped you for a reward.
아, 그렇군요. 모든 것에 대한 보답으로 공주님이 원하시는 것을 뭐든 드리고 싶습니다.
Oh, right. To show our gratitude, we'd like to give you anything you want.
뭐든 좋아? 그럼 나 슌노스케 씨를 저...
Is anything alright? Then I'd like to have Shunnosuke as...
오.
Hey.
아버지?
A father?
여보, 축하드려요.
Congratulations, dear.
고마워, 카즈에.
Thank you, Kazue.
이게 무슨...
No way...
그래서 센히메 님, 슌노스케 씨를 저 다음엔 무엇입니까?
So, Senhime, how would you want Shunnosuke?
아, 그게, 그러니까 슌노스케 씨 부인을, 그러니까...
Oh, that... I mean that to have Shunnosuke's wife as...
아, 맞아! 슌노스케 씨하고 부인에게 포상을 준다는 거지!
Oh, right! Have Shunnosuke and his wife to receive rewards!
이제 됐어.
Never mind.
그렇게 울지 마시오. 그 일이 있은 이상 어떻게든 좋은 일이 일어날 것이오.
Don't cry like that-dasu. Something good will happen soon after all that-dasu.
그렇습니다! 옛날부터 남겨진 자에게는 복이 있다고 하지 않습니까.
That's right! They say that leftovers will be more fortunate than others.
남겨진 자? 코지로, 내가 나머지라고 말하는 거야?!
Leftover? Kojirō, are you saying that I'm a leftover?!
아, 아니, 그런 의미가...
N- no, I didn't mean that...
그래, 어차피 난 나머지다!
Yeah, I am a leftover after all!
멈춰!
Stop!
결국에 가공할 위력을 가진 이도류를 완성했다.
He finally developed the technique of dual blades boasting a fearsome potency.
힘내라, 무사시! 지팡구 넘버원의 무예가가 되어라!
Keep it up, Musashi! Become the number one martial artist of Jipangu!
カラのポケットに　ツキが
飛び込むことも　あるさ
おっきな声で　笑えば
あしたには　朝が来る
無くすものなんか　何もないさ
やっちゃえ！イケイケ！
手ぶらは　強いぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
人生　てなもんさ　チャンスが　ほら
しっぽを振って　追ってくるぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
未来も　てなもんさ　あしたが　ほら
両手ひろげて　笑ってるぜ
경비로 취직한 바이켄하고의 재회도 순간.
We meet Baiken once again, and he got a job of guard.
영주님이 요괴 누에에게 시달리고 하오.
The feudal lord seems to be having trouble with a monster Nue.
이렇게 된 바 우정을 위해 발벗고 나서지 않으면 사내의 체면이 떨어지오!
For our friendship, I must act to help, or it would bringing shame upon myself-dasu!
누에 퇴치에 뛰어들었는데 그 뒤에 오니히메의 모습이!
We join to get rid of that Nue-dasu, and Onihime is behind!
다음 이야기! 누에가 우는 밤은 무섭소
Next story! The Night that Nue Cries is Scary-dasu.
질풍노도의 우정파워이오!
It's the stormy power of friendship-dasu!
다음 이야기
누에가 우는 밤은 무섭소
기대하세요!
Next Episode
The Night that
Nue Cries is Scary
Look forwards for it!